(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-08T22:54:50.153680",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
今日の3Dお披露目はー？
Today's 3D showcase is...?
ラオーラが3Dで初登場！
Raora makes her 3D debut!
チャッティーニランドにやってきたラオーラが...
Raora has arrived at Chattini Land...
ジェットパックをかけて、ミニゲームで大暴れ！
She goes wild in mini-games to get a jetpack!
泣いて...
Crying...
Please, please, give me the ticket!
怒って...
Getting angry...
I'm done with this! I'm so done! I'm leaving!
セクシーなラオーラも見れちゃう！？
We might even see a sexy Raora?!
もちろん歌も歌っちゃうよ！
Of course, she'll even sing!
そして、まさかのファイト・喧嘩もしちゃって...
And even unexpected fights and arguments...
ジェットパックは手に入るのかな？
Will she be able to get the jetpack?
ラオーラ・パンテーラの3Dお披露目、始まるよー！
Raora Panthera's 3D showcase starts now!
Ciao! Ciao, Raora!
Are you recording me?
What should I look... what should I look...
What is this place?
Oh my god! That's a... that's a giant Chattini on the castle!
Oh my gosh! Look at the one in the fountain! Oh, that's so pretty! And there's another one over there!
And another one over there!
Wait a second... Is this... Is this...
Is this Chattini Land?!
That's so cool!
Hey, cameraman, come here, come here, come here.
How do I look in 3D, huh?
You should take a look too...
to my Chattino! Look at him! Isn't he so pretty? So cute, right?
Oh, and you also should take a look to... my tail!
Ooh! Big cat means big tail!
What do you think? How do I look?
Hey, Raora! Raora, Raora, Raora!
Hey, hey, hey! Whoa, whoa, whoa! Oh...
Chattino! Oh... What did you do?
Oh, come here now! I'm gonna... I'm gonna use my weapon!
Yeah, come here! How dare you? How dare you knock me down like this?
ちょっと待って！！言いたいことがあるんだ！
Wait a second!! I need to tell you something!
Huh? Eh? You can... You can talk? Oh, that's impressive.
Well, I'm guessing you need me for something? What do you need?
そう、欲しいものがあるんだけど… チャッティーニランドのミニゲームを全部クリアしないと手に入らないんだ！
Yeah. There's this thing we want, but... The only way you can get it is by clearing all the Mini-Games here in Chattini Land!
Mini-games?
Something... you can only get here by clearing mini-games...
I think I know what it is.
あれだよ、あれ！
It's... that thing over there!
Eh? Eh?
Ah! Oh! I knew it! It's a jetpack! Oh!
Oh, the Chattini want one so badly, right?
僕たちだけじゃ手に入れられないから、手伝ってラオーラ！お願い！
We can't get it on our own, though, so help us out Raora! Please!
Ah, are you begging me?
Well, you know, little one...
No! I told you I'm not giving you the jetpack! So, I'm leaving. Bye-bye.
お願い！お願い！お願いーーー！
Please! Please! Pleeeease!
Ah, are you following me? Oh...
Well... I guess... it's a special day after all.
You know what? I'll give it a shot!
やったーーー！
Yaaaaay!
Okay then, what should I do here?
ミニゲームはこのエリアにあるから、がんばってね！
The game's in this area of the land, so good luck!
Okay then. You know what? I'm gonna do my very best! Well, I should go then.
Gamba-Raora! Rawr! Whoa!
あ、待って。右はあっちだよ。
Oh, wait. The right way is over there.
Eh? Eh? I mean...
Ah! I'm heading out. Gamba-Raora! Rawr!
この番組はご覧のスポンサーの提供でお送りいたします
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
死ぬまでピュアピュアやってんのん？
Gonna be a smitten mitten 'til the day you die?
Love, bluh bluh bluh
Love, bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh
ラブと超ライク パーティションはない、ない
Love and super-like, the lines of separation are nil, nil
きみだけが特別じゃないんだ
It’s not like you're super-duper special
反省とかあたしに求められても
You want me to repent? What can I say?
ほんと病んだり勘違いしないで
Don't get depressed, or get perplexed or vexed, okay?
で？で？で？
And? And? And?
どうしてなんで期待の戸締まり忘れるの？
Why do you always forget to lock the door on expectations?
最初にあれほどやめときなって伝えたじゃん
I told you from the start, don't even try
お純情様、あちらが出口ですが
Little miss devotion, the exit's over there
やっぱ帰りたくない…ですか？
Oh, so not going home after all?
ホップステップ う〜、ワンモアチャンス！
Hop, step, ooh, one more chance!
もうやっぱアピってラビったらいいじゃん
Why don't you kiss up and shake your cottontail?
POPな愛撫 謳ったらいいじゃん
A pop cuddle snuggle, hum a tune why don't you?
みっともないから嫉妬仕舞いな
It's out of place, put away your jealousy
発火しちゃうとかくっそだせえな
Thirsty? Ugh, so corny!
淋しくなったら誰でもいいじゃん
If you get lonely, anyone will do, just get lucky
埋まればいいじゃん 埋まればいいじゃん
Just fill it in, just fill it in
嫌嫌愛して生きたくなって 死ぬまでピュアピュアやってんのん
I loathed to love, but it gave me life, gonna be a smitten mitten 'til the day you die?
やっぱアピってラビったらいいじゃん
So why don't you kiss up and shake your cottontail?
BADなダンス 腫魔ったらいいじゃん
A bad dance, why don't you drown in it?
やっぱり好きとかやってられんわ
Fake out! I like you! Ugh, can’t take it
馬鹿じゃない？嗚呼くっそ鬱雑えわ
You nincompoop! Such a pesky beast!
淋しくなったら誰でもいいじゃん
If you get lonely, anyone will do, just get lucky
埋まればいいじゃん 埋まればいいじゃん
Just fill it in, just fill it in
底底愛して死にたくなって こちとらフラフラやってんのん、OK？
Fell in love with a meh and felt like dyin', so I'm just smashin' over here, okay?
「はーい」
“Roger that!”
Love, bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh bluh
バーストからインスタントラヴァー
Burst and scramble, we're instant lovers
頭＋身体がばかに絡まらあ
Body and mind, wrapped and twisted in stupid
ゴーストならアンデッドマナー
The dearly undead, be a ghost, that's the rules
嗚呼未だ淫ら 今は火花散らばそれがアンサー、だ
Peekaboo, knock-knock, alight that hibana, that's the answer, 'kay?
バーストからインスタントラヴァー
Burst and scramble, we're instant lovers
頭＋身体がばかに絡まらあ
Body and mind, wrapped and twisted in stupid
ゴーストならアンデッドマナー
The dearly undead, be a ghost, that's the rules
嗚呼未だ淫ら 今は火花散らばそれがアンサー、だ
Peekaboo, knock-knock, alight that hibana, that's the answer, 'kay?
う〜、ワンモアチャンス！
Ooh, one more chance!
もうやっぱアピってラビったらいいじゃん
Why don't you kiss up and shake your cottontail?
POPな愛撫 謳ったらいいじゃん
A pop cuddle snuggle, hum a tune why don't you?
みっともないから嫉盗仕舞いな
It's out of place, put away your jealousy
発火しちゃうとかくっそだせえな
Thirsty? Ugh, so corny!
淋しくなったら誰でもいいじゃん
If you get lonely, anyone will do, just get lucky
埋まればいいじゃん 埋まればいいじゃん
Just fill it in, just fill it in
嫌嫌愛して生きたくなって 死ぬまでピュアピュアやってんのん
I loathed to love, but it gave me life, gonna be a smitten mitten 'til the day you die?
やっぱアピってラビったらいいじゃん
So why don't you kiss up and shake your cottontail?
BADなダンス 腫魔ったらいいじゃん
A bad dance, why don't you drown in it?
やっぱり好きとかやってられんわ
Fake out! I like you! Ugh, can’t take it
馬鹿じゃない？嗚呼くっそ鬱雑えわ
You nincompoop! Such a pesky beast!
淋しくなったら誰でもいいじゃん
If you get lonely, anyone will do, just get lucky
埋まればいいじゃん 埋まればいいじゃん
Just fill it in, just fill it in
底底愛して死にたくなって こちとらフラフラやってんのん
Fell in love with a meh and felt like dyin', so I'm just smashin' over here
やっぱアピってラビったらいいじゃん
So why don't you kiss up and shake your cottontail?
とっくのとうに終わったおもいで
A memory that ended long ago
みっともないとか言ってごめんな
Sorry for calling you out of place
発火したいけどもうだめなんだ
I want to ignite but it's no good anymore
淋しくなったら誰でもいいじゃん
If you get lonely, anyone will do, just get lucky
埋まればいいじゃん 埋まればいいじゃん
Just fill it in, just fill it in
否否愛して生きたくなって こちとらフラフラやってんのん、OK？
Saying no to love but wanting to live, so I'm just smashin' over here, okay?
「はーい」
“Roger that!”
やあ やあ やあ 悪い子さん
Well, well, well, bad little child
まあ まあ まあ お愛顧じゃん
There, there, there, you're the favorite, right?
さあ さあ さあ 始めるよ
Now, now, now, let's get it started
もっとこの穴を愛してよ
Love this hole even more
やあ やあ やあ 悪い子さん
Well, well, well, bad little child
まあ まあ まあ お愛顧じゃん
There, there, there, you're the favorite, right?
さあ さあ さあ 始めるよ
Now, now, now, let's get it started
もっとこの穴を愛してよ
Love this hole even more
だっせ
So lame
Chattini Land Flower Garden Area
Wow! Look at this place!
I was not expecting to play a game in such a pretty place.
And... I wonder what kind of game it's gonna be.
Raora!
This is your conscience.
Eh? My conscience? Do I have one? Oh, Mori?
Yo! Yo, Raora! It's your turn.
Yo, Raora! Say something, say something.
Ra- Ra- Raora...
Is that... is that... is that a ghost, or what is that? Where is...?
Where is...? I can't... I can't see anyone.
Ra- Ra- Raora!
Is that a hug?
Hey! It's a group hug!
Congrats, Raora, on your 3D debut!
Thank you! We're so happy for you.
Oh, thank you so much! I'm so happy to be here!
Congrats! Yay!
Yay! Thank you!
Cute, cute! Thank you!
No, you're cute! No, you're cute!
No, you! No, you!
No way!
Well, as you may have assumed by our grand entrance over here...
...your opponents for this mini-game are, as you see...
*coughs* Mina-san! Mori Calliope from hololive English's first generation, Myth.
*coughs* Everyone! Mori Calliope from hololive English's first generation, Myth.
If you don't know me, now you do. Who's over here?
Konnichibabe! This is Ouro Kronii from hololive English -Promise-...
...and look at this beautiful woman.
Wait, who could this beautiful woman be? Dare desu ka?
Wait, who could this beautiful woman be? Who is she?
Yes! Thank you!
Ah, kochi kochi! Kochi, kochi, kochi, kochi!
Ah, over here, over here! This way, this way!
Yubi, yubi! hololive kara kimashita Inugami Korone yoroshiku ne!
Yubi, yubi! From hololive, I'm Inugami Korone! Nice to meet you!
Whoo! Yoroshiku!
Whoo! Nice to meet you!
Yoroshiku! Yoroshiku!
Nice to meet you! Nice to meet you!
Korone-senpai, hajimemashite!
Korone-senpai, nice to meet you!
Hajimemashite!
Nice to meet you!
Kyou wa kite kureて arigatou gozaimasu!
Thank you so much for coming today!
Ah, nihongo jouzu!
Ah, your Japanese is so good!
Yay, yeah, yeah!
Thank you! So, Mori...
What kind of game are we gonna play today?
Well, get ready, because it's time for...
One, two, three, say cheese!
(Cheering)
Say Cheese! Raora!!
Yeah yeah! All right!
Now then, here are the rules.
Chattinis are going to...
...jump out of the bushes at random intervals...
...to snap a photo of you!
And when they do so,
you've got to enter the frame and then...
...strike a specific pose for them!
Oh, okay, okay. Sounds easy.
Like that, like that. Just move into the camera frame...
...and strike the pose once the Chattinis jump out!
Okay, wait, wait. And...
Oh, that is... That is...
That's a good example, yes! Exactly!
She's a little too hyped for that. I know!
Hurry up!
No, no, no, you have to be competitive.
And well, as you have seen,
Raora clears if she can strike five poses...
...at the designated locations within the time limit!
Easy, right?
I got it!
It sounds so fun, let's go!
Yeah, but it's not going to be easy.
Yeah, it's not going to be easy because...
...we're going to be taking part as well,
and I'm gonna get in your way! No, I'm gonna get in your way!
I'm gonna get in your way!
All up in your...
Well, that's what you think.
I'm gonna get the ticket, I'm gonna win!
No.
Yes.
I guess that means we're all gonna get...
Loser! Raora loser!
No, I'm not a loser! You're a loser!
Yo, no, no, no!
Well, I feel like everyone's confident. Very confident!
A little too confident.
No, don't worry, it's okay, it's all good, it's all good!
We're striking a pose, it's a pose game!
It's a pose game!
Got it, got it! Yeah, yeah!
Are you guys excited?
We're so excited!
Okay, if everybody's ready then,
let's do this!
Let's do it!
Who will Win?!
Hope you're all ready, troops! Are you guys excited?
Yeah!
Get ready to start voguing.
Since it would be a shame to go straight into the real thing,
let's do some practice first, okay?
Okay, okay, let's do it.
All right. So, here we go.
Three, two, one, start!
Okay, let's see. First camera...
Ah, here, here, here! Hey hey hey!
Oh, so close! No, no, no!
Where is it? Where is it?
Yo, yo, yo! No, no, no!
Okay, uh, okay, let's see.
Next camera... Yes, yes! This is Calliope's time to shine!
One more!
Oh, here, here! Hey hey hey!
Where? Where? Where? Where?
Aha! No!
Get away!
Dang it!
Are you doing okay there, buddy?
That was so good!
I will touch you. And I will hurt you.
Just so we're all on the same page, I will hurt you if I have to.
Hurt me! I love it!
I love that. That is not the response I expected.
Well, that was fun, though.
Shall we move on to the main event, ladies?
Okay! Yes!
Okay. The time limit for the main event is two minutes.
Whoever strikes the right pose in the required spots most is the winner.
Now then,
let's get this show on the road. Three, two...
...one, let's go!
Game Start! Ha! Ha!
Where is it? Oh, here!
That was kind of neat! Let's go, let's go!
Where is it?
No, no, no, no, no!
Ahaha, we did it. Let's go!
Oh man, I'm gonna get pictured. Yo, yo, yo, yo!
No! Get away!
Missed! Dang it.
Next one is mine! Where is it?
What do you think? As I said, I will hurt you.
No! Korone!
Man, everyone's so good.
I know.
At, you know, hurting each other. Don't get it!
Oh my god. Where is it?
Uh! No, no, no, no, no!
Don't! No!
大丈夫、先輩？大丈夫ですか？
Are you okay, Senpai? Are you okay?
It's okay, it's okay!
No! No, no, no, no!
Oh! Go!
Go! Ah!
Why is she so strong?
She's rejecting all of my pushes!
No!
We're safe!
Nice!
Okay. Oh man.
Okay.
Really blocking...
Man, I'm not even gonna try on this one.
This is bad.
Next.
There we go.
While they're all squabbling,
Calliope takes the lead.
Yes! Ha!
That's so tiring.
Nice! No!
No, not every time! You can't get it every time, Kronii.
Oh, yeah!
Come on.
No, wait. Wait, let me...
Help me!
I have to have... this one.
Times up! No!
No!
おいおいおい…
Hey, hey, hey...
That's so tiring. Yo, why are you all so strong?
I don't get it.
Are you dead?
Ah, I'm dead.
Raora?
So tired.
Yeah. Are you good?
We are good.
Oh...
Oh, Kronii's so good.
So good!
Man, I feel like we just had a... psycho battle.
We had a battle.
I'm dead.
Raora!
I'm good.
Good job.
Raora! That's what I call...
...good job.
Okay.
Okay. How was it?
How do you guys think that you did?
I think I won. Good job, good job.
I think I won. Me there.
Oh, no, no, no. Me there.
I think Kronii won.
With the sheer force of her muscles pushing people out of the way.
With the sheer face of her muscles pushing people out of the way.
I'm so sorry!
And it wasn't even that. She can't be pushed. I mean, hey, you know what, competitive spirit.
I can't even argue with that.
Well then.
Well done, everyone.
Well done.
Well, let's see how that weighs up against the results, shall we?
Yay!
I bet I am the winner.
No, no, no, Raora, Raora, Raora!
Yes, Kronii. Yes, Kronii. Me, me, me, me win!
Yes, Kronii win!
No, no, no, let me win. Me, me, me.
All right, all right, let's see how we all did then. Here we go.
Okay.
Drum roll, please. Drum roll.
And the winner is...
Kronii!
Yay! No way!
No!
That crazy clock is just strong.
Man, congrats.
Congrats, congrats.
I knew that Kronii win.
Thank you. Thank you.
There was no defeating the clock.
The clock of steel, oh my God.
This is rigged, it's rigged!
She's too good, Raora. She can't be beaten. I tried to pick her up and move her and she just can't be...
...she can't be moved, she's immovable.
Man, it's really too bad though, I was gonna give you the ticket if you managed to win, but oh well, this round's a bust.
All boo-hoo, so sad, oh, I cry.
No!
Wait, wait, wait, wait a second. There must be a way, right? I need the ticket. I need to clear the game.
Please, please.
I mean...
It's not... it's not up to me, but you know what? What to do, what to do. I feel kind of bad, you're my cute kouhai.
Please.
Korone-senpai! Korone-senpai, what should we do?
Yeah, let's see. Um, do you like Japanese TV show?
Yeah, let's see. Um, do you like Japanese TV shows?
Yes, I love Japanese TV show, yes.
Yes, I love Japanese TV shows, yes.
Uh, please, cute onedari?
Uh, please make a cute plea?
Eh? Onedari? Cute onedari.
Huh? A plea? A cute plea.
You want me to beg? Yeah, onedari. Oh, this, this camera, okay? This camera.
You want me to beg? Yeah, make a plea. Oh, this camera, okay? This camera.
Right here. Ah, ちょっと低い、ちょっと低く、ちょっと低く。
Right here. A bit low, a bit low, a bit low.
Get kind of low, like you're being super sweet.
Eyes up, eyes up, okay? Oh, okay.
Do your best. Cute face, cute face, okay?
Cute face. I can't wait. Okay, onedari, onedari.
Cute face. I can't wait. Okay, plea, plea.
Cute onedari.
A cute plea.
Raora's Cute Plea!
Uh, three, two, one, action!
Please.
Please, Korone-senpai.
Onedari.
I'm pleading with you.
Please, give me the ticket.
Please, I need the ticket.
Please.
Please, Korone-senpai, お願いします！
Please, Korone-senpai, I'm begging you!
Please!
Please, give me the ticket.
Oh man, I feel so bad now.
I need the ticket.
I didn't think she would go this far. Yes, my 3D debut.
All right, all right, all right. You've done enough, you've done...
You want it that much?
All right, all right, all right, Raora. You've done it. Here's the ticket. Look at your hand, look at your hand.
Okay.
Yay, ticket! Thank you, senpai! Great job.
Excellent onedari.
Excellent pleading.
Yay! Excellent onedari, okay.
Yay! Excellent pleading, okay.
There you go.
I got the ticket! Let's go!
Well done. See? No problem. Happy ending.
Happy ending! Now then...
You will receive the Jetpack Chatini if you gather up three tickets. Count 'em, three.
So good luck on the next games as well.
Thank you, senpai! Thank you!
Yeah, no problem. Thank you so much.
Now go do your best. Okay.
I'll do my best. Thank you so much.
Go play! Bye, go play!
Yay, go play!
This way! Go straight!
Go straight.
This way, this way, this way, go straight!
Let's go!
Bye! Bye-bye!
See you! Bye-bye! See ya!
チャッティーニランド ジャングルエリア
[Chattini Land - Jungle Area]
Oh my gosh, this area is really different from the last one!
It's super dark! And what's with all the bars?
It's... it's kind of scary...
What is that?
I hear voices!
Is... is that a ghost? What is that?
Oh my gosh! Oh!
Please spare me! Please, my time has come!
Please take my soul! Are those ghosts?
Or is...
Is it Nerissa and Moona?!
Yeah, you're going to say you don't recognize us?
Oh, of course I recognize you! Hello!
Congratulations on your 3D! Thank you!
Thank you! I'm so happy! Thank you!
I think we have to introduce ourselves!
Of course! Starting with me!
Hello everyone! I am Moona Hoshinova from hololive Indonesia Gen 1!
Hi darlings! This is hololive English Advent's devilish diva, the one and only Nerissa Ravencroft! Thank you for having me!
Thank you so much for being here!
We come here to bring a game!
A game?! Really?
It involves cooperation. Cooperation? That sounds good!
What are we going to do? What are we going to do?
Well, the game this time is...
One, two, three... Limbo Dance Panthera!
The rules are super simple.
The three of us are going to do some sexy limbo dance.
Dancing, yes, the limbo dance, dancing...
...as we make our way towards the stage.
Yay! So excited!
Me too! And once we're there, there's one thing left to do.
We are all going to sing a super awesome trio song!
So happy!
Sounds simple, right? Sounds simple, let's see.
I am... I'm born for this! Let's go!
But, you know, are we really going to be able to do this?
I think we might have not thought ahead too far.
Of course we are going to do it!
No, but, you know, we all have something...
...that I feel like will make the limbo...
...a little bit difficult.
Oh, don't worry about it! Something that is really, really hard, but it's fine! We can do it!
Save that for the game, ladies! Okay.
Let's do it!
First of all, we need to do some warmup. Oh!
Yeah! Yes, keep going, girls!
Woo!
Yeah! Let's warmup a little bit before the game starts.
クリアできるのか？！
Can They Clear It?!
Right! Let's get really hot, girls!
I took off my jacket because it's so hot in here!
Can you do me a favor? Of course!
Could you jump a little bit more? Just a little bit.
Yes! Yes, like this!
And look at those shoulders, too! Show those off! Very nice!
Thank you!
Oh my god!
I'm going to do my very best in limbo dance!
Let's do it, then! Let's do it!
Get the music going! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
ゲームスタート！
Game Start!
Oh! Nice music, we hear! Yeah!
Are you ready? I'm ready!
It's your 3D video, so get going!
Well, that's too easy for me! Are you guys ready? Yes!
Okay, here we go!
Yay!
I'm going next!
Moona!
Easy for her! Yes!
Nerissa! Nerissa, you can do it! Oh my god!
Easy peasy!
Who's next? Who's next? Same order!
Same order, we'll keep it going! That's a little bit unfair!
Well, I'm going to do it, then! Show us how it's done!
Yay! Good job!
Okay. I can do it!
Easy, easy! Look at you go!
Okay. Nerissa, Nerissa... Oh! Good! Easy game!
This is a little bit more difficult. Maybe same order? Maybe...
Senpai order! / I can do it for you, girl.
Okay... Woo!
Ooh! / Look at her go!
Look at her! / Nice!
Next up... / You can do it. Watch how it's done.
Show me clean.
Whoa! / That's so clean, girl!
Let's go! My turn! Definitely going to do it.
Come on, kohai.
Whoa! / Oh! Oh! Good! So good!
Okay, maybe switch it up. I'll go first. / Yeah, she goes first.
Maybe... / Oh my god!
She's nailing it. Are we going to be able to do it, though? I don't know.
I believe. / You can do it. I can't do it. This is really tough one.
You can do it. Ooh! Success!
You actually did it!
All right, my turn! Let me show you all my skills!
You can do it, Raora! / Ha!
Oh! Oh, no!
Oh, good, I'm good, I'm good. / You're okay, you're okay. / Cut it, cut it.
No, we have to keep going. There's still two more!
Keep going. Let me rest a little bit.
Oh my god, I'm too old for this. / Come here, Mama, come here.
Who had this kind of idea of the game? Two more times, though.
Two more. Come on, come on. / Let's go.
We have two more to go, right? Wait a second... You dropped yours?
Oh, no! / Well, I think I'm done with these two, then.
Oh, go for it. / I think I still can keep it for now.
Time to get serious. So, I'm going to lock in. / This is impossible, though.
Yeah, it's a little bit low, but I think we can do it. / Okay. I'll try first.
Oh! Oh! Ooh!
She's too good, Moona! / I don't know if I can do it.
Oh my god. / Okay, come on. You can do it. You can do it. Come on, Moona!
No, I think... I have an idea. / You have an idea?
Oh!
That's a great idea! / The power of my red hand!
Let's see. / You can do it.
Come on, Raora. You got this. Okay.
I think I can do it. Ooh!
Tada! / That's great! / That's really nice.
Okay, I don't think I can... I don't know if I can do this one.
Uh, I mean, you did so good so far. / You can do it! One more! One more!
I think I'm too tall for this one. I'm going to fall. / I'm gonna hold you, I'm gonna hold you.
Oh, oh, oh!
I did it! I'm going to follow the way. I'm going to follow her way.
Yes. Let's do this.
We're gonna do it. She's getting serious. She's getting serious!
Whoa! Oh, okay!
Whoa! Oh my god!
My back hurts!
Okay, okay. Then, it's my turn now. What to do...
Well, I'm a big cat, so...
Nya, nya!
Nya, nya, cute face!
Here you go. / Thank you!
Well, I still think we have one more obstacle yet before us.
Where, where, where? / Look at the slope. We've got to go up.
Oh, let's go! / All right, everyone.
Don't forget our limbo dance. / Oh, yeah. Limbo dance, now. Hello!
Let's go to the stage. / Are you guys excited?
Yeah! So excited! I am so ready!
Oh my god, that was so tiring.
Yeah. But we did it! / We're here!
We're here! / Are you ready for this?
I don't know what I'm doing, but let's do it! / We've got to go. So cold!
All right, let's start! / Yay!
[Song: Cutie Panther]
捕まえちゃう！
I'll capture you!
(どこにいるの？ ムリよムリよ どこにいたってムリよ)
(Where are you? It's useless, useless! Wherever you are, it's useless!)
捕まえちゃう！
I'll capture you!
(だれといるの？ ダメよダメよ わたし以外はダメよ)
(Who are you with? No way, no way! Anyone but me is a no-way!)
甘いよ甘い そんな装備じゃ
You're too naive! With gear like that...
逃げられるわけ無いじゃないか
there's no way you can run away!
狙いをつけて
I'll take aim...
密かに背後から
secretly from behind.
I love you
私のことを好きになるはず
you're bound to fall in love with me.
I love you
そこに正義があるの
there is justice in that.
何度も言わせるつもりなの？ おやおや
How many times do I have to say it? Oh my, oh my...
抵抗するならしてごらん！ いがいと
Go ahead and try to resist! Surprisingly...
我が儘だと知ってるけれど
I know I'm being selfish, but...
私の方が上手なようね
it seems I have the upper hand.
冷たい言葉 優しい視線
Cold words, a gentle gaze...
獲物は...君だよ！
My prey... is you!
Cutie Panther 私
Cutie Panther, I'll...
どこでも行くよ
go anywhere!
君の 君の 心盗んでみせるよ
I'll steal your, steal your heart, you'll see!
Cutie Panther 私
Cutie Panther, I'll...
どこでも行くよ
go anywhere!
君の 君の 心を離さない
I will never let go of your heart!
熱いよ熱い 愛のルールは
It's hot, so hot! The rules of love...
破られるため在るんだよ
exist to be broken.
ずるい罠へと誘う微笑みは
A smile that lures you into a sly trap...
I miss you
好きのせいだし悪くないでしょ
it's because I love you, so it's not bad, right?
I miss you
それが重度の恋よ
that's what a severe case of love is.
絶対全てをいただくよ？ おやおや
I'll definitely take everything, you know? Oh my, oh my...
反抗するならしてごらん！ てごわい
Go ahead and try to defy me! Tough luck...
偽りだって疑うよりも
Rather than suspecting it's a lie,
私の事信じてみてよ
just try believing in me.
優しい言葉 冷たい視線
Gentle words, a cold gaze...
獲物は...君だよ！
My prey... is you!
Cutie Panther 君の
Cutie Panther, I want...
瞳が欲しい
your eyes!
私 きっと きっと盗んでみせるよ
I'll surely, surely steal them, you'll see!
Cutie Panther 君の
Cutie Panther, I want...
瞳が欲しい
your eyes!
私 きっと 素早く逃がさない
I'll surely capture you quickly and never let you escape!
何度も言わせるつもりなの？ おやおや
How many times do I have to say it? Oh my, oh my...
抵抗するならしてごらん！ いがいと
Go ahead and try to resist! Surprisingly...
我が儘だと知ってるけれど
I know I'm being selfish, but...
私の方が上手なようね
it seems I have the upper hand.
冷たい言葉 優しい視線
Cold words, a gentle gaze...
獲物は...君だよ！
My prey... is you!
Cutie Panther 私
Cutie Panther, I'll...
どこでも行くよ
go anywhere!
君の 君の 心盗んでみせるよ
I'll steal your, steal your heart, you'll see!
Cutie Panther 私
Cutie Panther, I'll...
どこでも行くよ
go anywhere!
君の 君の 心を離さない
I will never let go of your heart!
捕まえちゃう！
I'm gonna catch you!
(どこにいるの？ ムリよムリよ どこにいたってムリよ)
(Where are you? No way, no way! Wherever you are, it's no use!)
捕まえちゃう！
I'm gonna catch you!
(だれといるの？ ダメよダメよ わたし以外はダメよ)
(Who are you with? No way, no way! No one but me is allowed!)
捕まえちゃう！
I'm gonna catch you!
(どこにいるの？ ムリよムリよ どこにいたってムリよ)
(Where are you? No way, no way! Wherever you are, it's no use!)
捕まえちゃう！
I'm gonna catch you!
(だれといるの？ ダメよダメよ わたし以外はダメよ)
(Who are you with? No way, no way! No one but me is allowed!)
Hah... Wow...
How was that, Velvet?!
That's really nice.
That's how Raora does it. So cool, right?
So together... happy!
Thank you for dancing and singing with me!
Ooh, and also since we already finished our session...
...so here is your ticket!
Yay!
Oh my god, I got it!
Congratulations, Raora!
Have just one more left now!
Yes! Thank you so much! I'm so happy!
It was so fun, thank you for having us!
Thank you! Good luck getting that final ticket too, alright?
Yeah, that's true! Our...
I'll do my best. I promise.
Thank you, girls.
You can do it!
Well, as for us, we should take our leave.
Bye-bye!
We must leave you.
Don't leave me, girls!
We need to go. No!
No!
They limbo danced so hard...
...that it became their default walking state!
Oh!
What is this place?!
Oh my god, this seems like...
...it came out of a sci-fi movie or something!
But now I'm curious.
What kind of game they got prepared for me this time?
Raora! Raora!
Eh? What is that? Eh?
What is this? Huh? Huh? Wait...
Wait a second!
I smell something...
Dog smell!
I know who you are! Come out!
Come here!
Raora!
Oh, come here, come here!
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
There, there, babies, there, there.
Oh, geez.
Nice hug, huh?
It's so nice!
Yay!
Oh, I'm so excited, I'm so nervous...
...I'm so happy!
Your tail is looking really happy, too!
No, no, no, no! No, no, no, no!
Okay, let's talk about it.
There's a game today, right?
Yes!
It's not the game, right? Okay, okay.
But why don't you guys introduce yourselves?
All right!
I'm not Mococo! I'm Fuwawa!
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo!
Together we are FuwaMoco!
Bau bau!
I'm not FuwaMoco!
No, you're not! Yes, I am!
I'm Koseki Bijou, the sparkling gem of hololive English -Advent-!
Kira kira! Koseki!
Yay!
And then... Raora!
It's still me, Raora Panthera from hololive English -Justice-, this time in 3D!
Yay!
Wait, have you introduced yourself before?
I'm not sure about that. Maybe.
Oh well, always good for hololive!
It's okay, it's okay.
So, what's the last game going to be?
Are you ready for this next game?
Actually, all of us...
...are the only ones in this tower!
What does that mean?
But we have a very important role too, right?
What? What are you guys going to do?
We're here... to stop you!
No, no, no, no, no!
You're going to let me win, right, girls?
We're gonna beat you up!
No, no, no, no! No, no, no, no!
You gotta let me win! It's my debut and it's the last ticket! I need it!
No, no, I don't think so.
We're gonna put you through the wringer, yeah!
Are you ready to hear what the third and final game is?
It is... No, no, no!
One! Two! Three!
Run! Run! Raora!!
Oh! Okay, okay. What are the rules?
Okay, are you curious? I'm very curious, yes.
Take a look at the conveyor belt behind you!
Oh! What is this? There's nothing on it, Biboo.
Oh, believe me, there is something on it!
Bring it out!
What is that? Oh! Ew!
Ew! What is... ew!
Ew! Is that a pizza?
Pineapple pizza!
Broken up spaghetti!
Ew, look at that! Ew! No, thank you!
Pasta with ketchup? No, no, no, no!
I'm done with this! I'm so done.
I'm leaving! I'm leaving!
I'm not going to play this game!
No, I'm not going to play this game.
It's too much for me!
No! No, no, no, no, no! It's too much for me! I'm done with this.
Well, do you notice that everything we've brought out here...
...is everything you hate?
Yeah, yeah!
And to clear, you're going to have to hop onto that stage and run, run, run!
And avoid everything! Got it?
Yep! You can do it!
And why are you guys here then?
What? What are you guys going to do?
Well... we'll be using certain things...
...to make life more difficult for you, Raora!
Yes, of course!
No, you guys really are criminals.
Stop, no. No, you're not going to do this to me.
Whoa! Let's go grab them!
Yeah, yeah, okay, okay! We'll be right back!
No, don't! No, don't!
What are they going to do? No, no, no, no, no...
Onion!
Cucumber!
Pasta! Pasta! Pizza!
No, no, no! Okay, okay, okay!
I will play the game! I will play the game!
You have to play the game! You have to play the game!
Okay, I will play the game!
Did you like that? 'Cause there's more where that came from!
No, no, don't touch me with that onion. It's bigger than you, Biboo!
Who are you calling "Biboo"? I'm bigger than this onion! This is a normal-sized onion!
Cucumbers are also big! Yum!
Now then, let's get going here!
Let's go, Raora!
All right, let's go!
Are you okay? Are you okay? I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine!
ラオラの運命は？！
Raora's Fate?!
Okay, you ready, Raora?
No, not so ready.
Wait, guys, guys, guys, can we play another game?
Okay, the timer's ready.
You need to keep dodging for 60 seconds to level up, okay?
Okay, okay, okay, I'm ready.
There's a total of three levels...
...so try to escape to the very end without getting hit, okay? Okay, okay, okay.
GAME START!
I'll do my best this time.
Level 1. Run, run!
Oh, no, the onion! Onion!
There's a pizza at the bottom!
No, no, no! Another onion!
Oh, my god, pasta! There is spaghetti!
No, no, spaghetti!
Watch out, Raora! Watch out!
Oh, my god! This is so hard!
Watch out, watch out! Watch out, watch out!
Ooh, big cat, big cat coming!
Wait, big cat?
Big ball!
No! Aah!
FAILED!
You failed already! No!
Do you want to try again?
One more time! One more time!
Last time! One more time! Yeah!
レベル1 リベンジ！
Level 1 Revenge!
How do you feel? Maybe we were a bit too harsh on her? That felt like a long time.
Yeah, it was unfair.
Okay then, we're going to set the clock to 30 seconds.
Does that sound more fair? Okay, let's do that then. I can definitely make it!
Okay, we're going to go again! Three, two, one...
...game start-o!
GAME START!
Aah! No! Run, Raora! Run!
Pizza!
No! Run, run! Run! No, onion!
No, don't get hit! No, no, no!
Wait, what is that? Is that a pasta?
Yes! Pasta!
Ooh, the pasta is so fast!
Three, two, one...
CLEAR!
Woohoo! Level 1 clear!
Yes, you did it, Raora!
I actually did it!
You did keep your goal, though. But that was just Level 1, you have Level 2 next!
Level 1 was too easy, you know.
Oh? Okay, well, let's try Level 2 then!
You can do it!
Just like the first time! Let's go!
Three, two, one, start!
GAME START!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Run, run!
Get ready!
Run! Wait!
Ah, watch out! Watch out!
Level 2!
Ten seconds!
Now, now, now! Go, go, go!
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
Wait! No!
Clear!
Yay! Level 2!
I did it, first try!
We cleared! Let's go!
I'm so good at the food dodge.
You know, you know...
You're not falling down or anything, huh?
Well, you know, maybe you didn't put enough effort.
Oh yeah? Okay, well, we're gonna make it harder then!
Let's get ready for...
Level 3!
No, no, no, no, no!
This is the last one. The ticket is mine.
Here we go to the next level. I think this one's going to be extra...
...hard.
Because you said that we weren't trying hard, you know what we're gonna do?
We're gonna make this one...
you only have one try.
Oh, come on!
And you know what, that's not all. It's gonna be extra hard!
What?! This is not a rule!
One try!
You guys are cheating!
This is not cheating, this is a game!
You are so evil.
All right, you better be preparing now.
We will see.
Okay...
Okay!
Here it comes!
Oh, she avoided it!
Oh, let's see, let's see.
Here it comes!
Oh, she's dodging so well! She's dodging!
Oh, she started so fast!
Look at her, look at her!
Watch out! Watch out! Watch out!
No! No! Aaaah!
Just like we said!
Yeah, she went really...
I don't think she's gonna be able to come back from that.
Yeah, it's over.
Bye bye!
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
Yosh yosh yosh yosh...
There, there, there, there...
Well, you know guys...
today is my 3D debut, right?
Yeah, yeah!
So, maybe, you know, senpais...
you guys could give me the ticket anyway?
No.
No! No! No.
Please! Ah!
I'm not getting the ticket?!
No, no ticket for you, sorry.
No!
But Raora, we have prepared a special stage for you!
Really? Wow!
Yeah, you know, while it was fun, you know, torturing you with things you hate...
...that was, that was really fun...
...you know, we kind of want to see your cool side.
My cool side?
Yeah! Your cool side!
You really want to see my cool side?
Go show it off to everybody!
Yeah, maybe you can put all those angry feelings into your next song!
Yeah, song! Yeah, sing!
Okay.
Okay, let's go, let's go!
Go, go, go, go!
恋は戦争
[Title: Love is War]
もう行き場がないわ
I have nowhere left to go
この恋の熱量
for the heat of this love...
Ah...
灰色の雲
Ashen clouds,
モノクロの喧騒
monochrome tumult.
日差しはかげり
The sunlight is shaded,
The sunlight is shaded
夕暮れは色を変えていく
and dusk changes colour.
嗚呼 世界がにじんで
Ah, the world gets blurry,
それでも好きでいられるかなんて
but can I really stay in love?
わかってる けどどうすればいいの
I get it, but what should I do?
どうしたら どうすれば
What am I meant to do? What should I do?
バカだな わたし……
I'm such a fool...
始めるのよ これは戦争
I'll kick things off. This is war!
嬉しそうなキミをみるなんて
As if I'll watch you while you seem so happy.
切なる恋 それは罪
Eager love is a crime.
見せてあげる わたしの想いを
I'll show you how I feel.
叫んでみたメガホンは
I tried screaming since my megaphone...
壊れてたの
...was broken.
どれだけ背伸びしたって
No matter how much I stretched myself,
君の視界に入らない
you didn't see me.
嗚呼 いつの間にか晴れた空
Ah, when did the sky get so clear?
全然似合わない
It doesn't feel right at all.
気持ちが抑えられなくて
I can't hold my feelings back.
どうしたら どうすれば
What am I meant to do? What should I do?
泣いてなんか ないんだからね
I'm not crying or anything!
大好き
I love you.
たたかうのよ ハートを撃て
I'll fight. I'll shoot hearts.
手段なんて選んでられない
I can't choose my means.
スカートひらり見せつけるのよ
I'll show off my fluttering skirt
君の視線奪ってみせるの
and steal your attention!
迎撃用意
Prepare to intercept.
戦況は未だ不利なのです
The war's current state is still unfavourable.
恋は盲目
Love is blind.
君の口づけで目が覚めるの！
Your kiss will wake me up!
Oh, I'm sorry, Chattini!
I tried my best, but I only got two...
Noooo... my jetpack...
Oh! Ohhh!
Ah... the jetpack exploded...
I'm sorry, Chattini!
Actually, I have a present for all of you!
Present? I wonder what it is? Is it a cucumber?
Uh, mm-mm. Let me tell you.
That's the best! It's not a jetpack but it's really nice!
Thanks, Chattini!
Well then, before I reveal the best present ever...
I've got an announcement to make! Ta-da!
Raora Pencil Case and Key Chain!
Yes! This is a cute pen case with me in a Chattino costume!
So I hope you guys can bring it everywhere—school, the office...
literally everywhere! So please don't miss it out, okay?
Ah, that was such a fun 3D showcase with a lot of things happening!
Did everyone have fun? Chattini, did you guys have fun?
Thank you! I'm so happy to hear that! Thank you!
Seems like you guys had a great time with me today. I'm so happy, thank you!
I'll keep doing my best to bring fun streams and more 3D live performances like this one today, okay?
I appreciate you guys so much! Thank you, Chattini, for all your support! Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Finally!
It's the long-awaited present from me
to everyone!
Are you guys ready?
The present is...
My first original song!
I'm so happy!
It's full of things I like,
and so many personal touches.
I worked really, really hard on this song,
so I hope you guys are going to
take a listen to it, okay?
Are you guys ready? Are you guys excited?
Let's go to the stage!
Uno! Due!
One! Two!
Gacha × Gacha ADVENTURE!
はい！はい！はい！Pon! Pon!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Pon! Pon!
Gacha, Gacha, RAOOOOOO!!
さあ、さあ、お宝探しだ
Come on, come on, let's find some treasure!
「今日は、ど〜んな獲物が見つかるかにゃ？」
"What kind of prey will we find today, nya?"
ほら、ほら、みんなと一緒に
Look, look, let's go with everyone!
「楽しい冒険、しゅっぱ〜つ！」
"Time to start our fun adventure!"
Un! Due! Tre!
One! Two! Three!
ハマっちゃったら抜け出せないの〜
Once you get hooked, you can't get out~
食べ物ぬいぐるみ
Food plushies,
PizzaもPastaも全部
pizza and pasta, all of them,
詰め込んだ魅惑の迷宮
stuffed into a fascinating maze!
ワクワク止まらない
My excitement won't stop!
Proviamo!
Let's try!
取れそうで取れなくてイライラ
クレーンゲーム
It seems easy but it's not,
a frustrating crane game!
「にゃ〜もう！」
"Oh, jeez!"
諦めたままリタイア
Giving up and retiring
するはずないじゃない！
is not an option!
「目指せコンプリート！」
"Aim for completion!"
さあ、もう一回 止めても無駄だよ
Come on, one more time!
It's useless to stop me!
もう一回 繰り返すデジャヴ
One more time! A repeating deja vu
諦めろって言わないで
Don't tell me to give up!
三度目の正直
Third time's the charm!
だから無問題 溢れる想いが
So no problem! My overflowing feelings...
とめらんない これって天職！？
...cannot be stopped. Is this my calling!?
楽しいことで満ちてる
Filled with fun things,
この先もずっと
from now on, forever!
「はい、せーのっ」
"Okay, ready, go!"
Gacha×Gacha ADVENTURE!
Gacha x Gacha ADVENTURE!
ガチャ...ガチャ...ガチャ...ガチャ...
Gacha... Gacha... Gacha... Gacha...
「ゲーム、リスタート！」
"Game, restart!"
グルグル回しまくっちゃえ
Spin it round and round!
「ダメだ...止まんない！」
"No way... I can't stop!"
お目当ての獲物が出るまで
Until the targeted prey comes out!
「お願い...もう一回！」
"Please... one more time!"
Bim bum bam!
ビートに乗ったら止まれないの〜
Once you get on the beat, you can't stop~
音ゲーもお手のもの
Rhythm games are a piece of cake too!
ComboもFeverも全部
Combo, Fever, all of them,
キメたら完璧Groove!
once nailed, it's a perfect Groove!
ズレたらゲームオーバーさ
If you're off, it's game over
Andiamo!
Let's go!
レースゲーム エンジン全開でアチアチ
Racing game, engine at full throttle,
burning hot!
白熱バトル！
Incandescent battle!
「いけいけ Go! Go! Go!」
"Go, go, Go! Go! Go!"
コーナーで差をつけたら
If we make a difference at the corner,
目指すは1位だー！
aim for 1st place!
さあ、もう一回 でも今日は終わり
Come on, one more time!
But today is over...
もう一回 言いかけて止まる
One more time, I start to say but stop
楽しかった気持ちが
The happy feelings
胸をキュッとするの
tighten my chest
ねえねえ、もうバイバイしなきゃダメ？
Hey, hey, do we really have to say goodbye already?
まだ帰りたくない
I don't want to go home yet
これって恋かな！？
Is this love!?
ワクワクで満ち溢れた
Filled with excitement,
この先の日々も
the days ahead as well...
「一緒に冒険しよう！」
"Let's adventure together!"
さあ、もう一回 止めても無駄だよ
Come on, one more time!
It's useless to stop me!
もう一回 繰り返すデジャヴ
One more time! A repeating deja vu
諦めろって言わないで
Don't tell me to give up!
何度でもチャレンジ
Challenge over and over again!
だから無問題 溢れる想いが
So no problem! My overflowing feelings...
とめらんない これぞ天職！！
...cannot be stopped. This is my true calling!!
何度でもやり直せる
We can start over as many times as we want
そう人生は
That's life!
「みんなも一緒に！」
"Everyone together!"
Gacha×Gacha ADVENTURE!
Gacha x Gacha ADVENTURE!
はい！はい！はい！Pon! Pon!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Pon! Pon!
Gacha, Gacha, RAOOOOOO!!
「また一緒に冒険しようね！Ciao ciao!」
"Let's adventure together again! Ciao ciao!"
That was so much fun!
How did you like it, Chattini? Did you like it?
Thank you for watching and listening!
Today was so much fun.
Thank you so much, everyone,
for all your support!
Thank you, thank you, Chattini, thank you!
I can't wait to see you all again!
Until next time...
Ciao ciao! Raora!
Raoooo!
Big cat means...
Big dreams!
Thank you Chattini for all your support!
I still can't believe this day finally came!
This is the very first step towards my idol dream,
and I will always do my best!
Let's keep going together to new chapters!
BIG CAT means BIG DREAMS!